Julia a dynamic general purpose programming language capable of high
Julia 是一种动态通用编程语言，能够
performance scientific Computing with high-level code it was created in 2012
使用高级代码进行高性能科学计算，它是由一群计算机科学家于 2012 年创建的，
by a gang of computer scientists who set out to build a language with the speed
他们着手构建一种具有
of C the dynamism of Ruby the practicality of python that can do
C 速度的语言、Ruby 的活力、python 的实用性 可以开箱即用地进行
statistics like R and linear algebra like Matlab out of the box it's a
R 之类的统计和 Matlab 之类的线性代数它是一种
general purpose language but is most well known for its use in numerical
通用语言，但最著名的是它在数值
analysis data visualization and machine learning it's extremely fast because
分析数据可视化和机器学习中的应用它非常快，因为
unlike most high-level languages it uses a just-in-time compiler to convert your
与大多数高级语言不同，它使用了一个just- 实时编译器在运行之前将您的
source code into machine code before running it and unlike most dynamic
源代码转换为机器代码，与大多数动态语言不同，
languages it has a flexible parametric type system that means static typing is
它具有灵活的参数类型系统，这意味着静态类型
optional by default and types can take parameters allowing one type to
默认是可选的，类型可以采用参数，允许一种类型
represent many different possibilities this opens the door to the multiple
表示许多不同的可能性，这将打开 多分派模式的大门，
dispatch pattern where one function can have multiple methods or implementations
其中一个函数可以有多个方法或
based on its input parameters and the language will determine which method to
实现 编辑其输入参数和语言将确定
dispatch at runtime in fact even operators like Plus or functions that
在运行时调度哪个方法实际上甚至像 Plus 这样的运算符或
use multiple dispatch to handle a variety of different type common Nations
使用多个调度来处理各种不同类型的通用函数
to get started install Julia then create a file ending in JL declare a variable
的函数开始安装 Julia 然后创建一个以 JL 结尾的文件声明
by providing a name then assign a value to it names support utf-8 encoding like
通过提供名称然后为其分配值的变量名称支持 utf-8 编码，如
emojis or mathematical symbols it uses symbols to represent built-in constants
表情符号或数学符号它使用符号来表示内置常量，
like Pi allowing you to write equations more elegantly in your code like Pearl
如 Pi，允许您在代码中更优雅地编写方程式，如 Pearl
it's very good at string parsing and supports multiple Expressions on a
它非常擅长 字符串解析并支持单行上的多个表达式，
single line resulting in tourists yet powerful code Define a function with the
从而产生游客但功能强大的代码 使用 function 关键字定义一个函数
function keyword and close it with the end keyword or shorten it to a single
并使用end 关键字将其关闭或将其缩短为
line with the equal sign or because functions are first class objects they
带有等号的单行，或者因为函数是它们可以的第一类对象
can be assigned to a variable or pass to another function anonymously what's
被分配给一个变量或匿名传递给另一个函数
interesting though is that by default a function is untyped which means it
有趣的是，默认情况下一个函数是unty  ped 这意味着如果函数被重新定义，它会
implements one method to handle all inputs if the function is redefined but
实现一种方法来处理所有输入，但是
this time with a type for the arguments another method is added to it when this
这次使用参数的类型，
function is called at runtime Julia will look at the type of the arguments and
在运行时调用此函数时会添加另一个方法 Julia 将查看参数的类型并
dispatch the corresponding method in addition we can pass a type as a
分派 相应的方法此外，我们可以将类型作为参数传递，
parameter then use keywords like where to perform Logic on the type itself in
然后使用关键字，例如 where对类型本身执行逻辑，在
this case it will assert that both types are the same now Julia is not an
这种情况下，它将断言这两种类型现在是相同的，但是 Julia 不是
object-oriented language in the classic sense however it does support composite
经典意义上的面向对象语言它确实支持
types with structs which contain multiple fields and optional types like
具有包含多个字段和可选类型的结构的复合类型，就像
any good scientific language it has very well thought out support for arrays with
任何优秀的科学语言一样，它经过深思熟虑地支持具有
many built-in functions to initialize and compute values over
许多内置函数的数组，以在多维数组上初始化和计算值
multi-dimensional arrays it supports asynchronous Computing with its task
它支持异步计算及其 任务
model which can pause and synchronize the execution of code like co-routines
模型，它可以暂停和同步代码的执行，例如
in other languages and finally when it comes to Big Data it can even distribute
其他语言中的协同程序，最后是 Bi  g 数据它甚至可以将
processing to multiple memory spaces or machines and run natively on a GPU this
处理分配到多个内存空间或机器上，并在 GPU 上本地运行
has been Julia in 100 seconds if you want to see more short videos like this
如果你想看更多像这样的短视频，100 秒内 Julia
hit the like button and subscribe thanks for watching and I will see you in the
next one
在下一个